<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="foto1">Met her on campus, she was originally from Lampung, the person was very kind. Our relationship is over because there was a third person</string>
    <string name="location">Bidan\'s Gang Number 93, Cipadung</string>
    <string name="foto2">Met her on action defending the people, she was elegant, strong, and understated. Our relationship is over because I could not marry her soon.</string>
    <string name="foto3">Beautiful diverting my world, from the real world into the unreal world. like our relationship which turned out to be unreal for a long time</string>
    <string name="foto4">Really like the sound, unfortunately when you sleep snoring, never again video call, he overslept instead snoring. our relationship is over</string>
    <string name="foto5">The athlete, bodybuilder, strong woman, she is the one. but because she underestimated me, I broke up with him.</string>
    <string name="foto6">She really likes fruits, especially bananas, really likes to suck bananas. our relationship is over because I couldn\'t give bananas every day</string>
    <string name="foto7">Food champions, anything to eat, but strangely never fat. like me, always slim, as slim as our relationship</string>
    <string name="foto8">Love snacks, hard to be told to eat heavy, sick. Our relationship is over, because she was sick</string>
    <string name="foto9">Ahh it\'s so bad to have a relationship with this creature, loveshopping, my wallet isn\'t strong. Our relationship is over, he preferred the rich from usury</string>
    <string name="foto10">The one are emotional, sometimes they cry easily, sometimes they get angry easily, I can\'t stand it when they\'re angry, they want to break up, I just break up</string>
    <string name="foto11">Our relationship foundered was just tired of the heart, whoever she hugged</string>
    <string name="foto12">It\'s only been 1 week already been decided, she said just like her</string>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="profile">Dev Information</string>
    <string name="asal">From :</string>
    <string name="nama">Name :</string>
    <string name="keahlian">Ability :</string>
    <string name="bela_diri">Self-defense</string>
    <string name="bela_umat">Defend the people</string>
    <string name="belanja">Shopping</string>
    <string name="berlari">Running</string>
    <string name="bernyanyi">Singing</string>
    <string name="jajan">Food a Snack</string>
    <string name="marah_marah">Grumpy</string>
    <string name="memakan">Eating</string>
    <string name="memasak">Cooking</string>
    <string name="memeluk">Hugging</string>
    <string name="mutusin">Broke Up</string>
    <string name="menghisap">Sucking</string>
    <string name="app_name">Ex-Girlfriend List</string>
</resources>